<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<module>
  <rawname>jointtechsconnector</rawname>
  <name>Jointtechs Connector</name>
  <version>1.0.23</version>
  <category>Connectivity</category>
  <publisher>Jointtechs</publisher>
  <license>GPLv3+</license>
  <licenselink>https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.txt</licenselink>
  <info>https://portal.joint.tech</info>
  <description>Jointtechs PBX agent for discovery, CDR/recording sync, live status, diagnostics, playback, approved forwarding management, supervision, and framework updates.</description>
  <!-- 1.0.23 restores direct PJSIP/SIP supervision first, rejects known originate failures, and reports the installed version correctly. -->
  <changelog>*1.0.21* Add duration-based and until-removed call forwarding with generation-safe timers and durable expiry reconciliation after PBX restarts.`n*1.0.20* Ring the supervisor through the FreePBX from-internal dialplan first while keeping OpDesk-style ChanSpy target options.`n*1.0.19* Match OpDesk supervision flow: originate directly to supervisor endpoint and ChanSpy the target channel base with qsE/qwsE/qBsE.`n*1.0.18* Prefer the full active channel name for supervision before uniqueid to avoid immediate spy hangups on PBXs with different concise field layouts.`n*1.0.17* Resolve the exact active Asterisk channel before Listen, Whisper, and Barge, then use ChanSpy against the channel uniqueid.`n*1.0.16* Add approved immediate removal for extension call forwarding from the portal.`n*1.0.15* Use FreePBX extension spying for Listen, Whisper, and Barge so the supervisor hears the selected active extension.`n*1.0.14* Ignore empty recording files during CDR sync so playback buttons only show for real audio.`n*1.0.13* Page historical CDR sync so large PBXs can import older calls without one oversized portal request.`n*1.0.12* Expand call sync to a deep historical CDR window so All Calls can include older PBX rows.`n*1.0.11* Add approved listen, whisper, and barge supervision commands for the live wallboard.`n*1.0.10* Allow larger live CDR batches to complete without portal request timeout.`n*1.0.9* Keep CDR sync on a rolling live window and resolve recordings only when files exist in approved recording paths.`n*1.0.8* Reinstall the automatic sync cron from heartbeat/config flows so calls keep syncing without manual resync.
*1.0.7* Add an approved read-only Asterisk active-channel probe for the live wallboard.
*1.0.6* Add SIP/PJSIP endpoint registration status for the live wallboard.
*1.0.5* Add approved temporary extension call forwarding from the portal.
*1.0.4* Include extension voicemail, follow-me, and call-forwarding inventory metadata.
*1.0.3* Fall back to the standard asteriskcdrdb database when FreePBX leaves CDRDBNAME empty, and return sanitized action errors for diagnostics.
*1.0.2* Let the public action endpoint load the connector class directly when FreePBX BMO lookup is unavailable, and install scheduled outbound call/recording sync.
*1.0.1* Install a public signed action shim for portal-triggered work when FreePBX blocks module PHP and authenticated AJAX.
*1.0.0* Add stable signed agent task runner, auto-registration, broad read discovery, dynamic CDR sync, deep recording discovery, log/file diagnostics, and signed self-update path.
*0.3.1* Add signed recording fetch action for temporary portal playback/download cache.
*0.3.0* Auto-register with the Jointtechs portal on install/config load, discover PBX metadata, and allow Jointtechs to assign the PBX to a customer later.
*0.2.2* Simplify pairing to pairing-code-first, auto-detect PBX public URL, default portal URL, and route signed portal actions through FreePBX ajax.php.
*0.2.1* Read recent FreePBX CDR rows, map native CDR fields, send recording paths, and make CLI sync workers functional.
*0.2.0* Add signed inbound read-only actions for portal-triggered heartbeat, sync, recording metadata refresh, and recording streaming.
*0.1.2* Fix install/uninstall returns, use FreePBX module config storage, sanitize AJAX pairing errors, and render pairing results inline.
*0.1.1* Implement real HTTPS pairing and move AJAX handlers into the main module class.
*0.1.0* Initial read-only pairing, heartbeat, CDR sync, and recording metadata sync scaffold.</changelog>
  <menuitems>
    <jointtechsconnector sort="90">Jointtechs Connector</jointtechsconnector>
  </menuitems>
  <depends>
    <version>16.0</version>
  </depends>
  <requirements>
    <module>core</module>
    <module>cdr</module>
  </requirements>
  <supported>16.0</supported>
</module>
